bizchickblogs.com 2012-10-14

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting BizChickBlogs.com. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used by BizChickBlogs.com.

**The Information We Collect**

Through BizChickBlogs.com websites and other media, you can subscribe to publications and purchase products, and engage in various activities like entering contests or sweepstakes, playing games, taking quizzes, voting in polls or otherwise expressing an opinion, subscribing to one of our services, such as newsletters, or participating in one of our online forums or communities. Your personally identifiable information may be required to engage in these activities as well as to receive products and services that you may have requested. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages and elsewhere include but are not limited to: name, address, gender, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number and credit or debit card information.  
We may also collect information about your personal or professional interests and use of various products, programs and services to qualify you for special publications or promotions. For instance, we may ask you to identify your job or industry to qualify you for free business magazines.

For certain promotions, you may be able to submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person’s name, mailing and/or e-mail address to send a gift or electronic greeting card. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages include: recipient’s name, address, e-mail address and telephone number.

We may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit our web pages or use our applications, such as the type of browser and operating system you are using, your IP Address and your Internet service provider.

**How We Use the Information**

We may use the information you provide about yourself or others to fulfill requests for our publications, products or services, to respond to inquiries about offerings and to offer other products, programs or services that may be of interest.

We may combine information we receive with outside records and share such information with third parties to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you.

If you choose to submit content (e.g., a guest post, feedback, letter to the editor, or an online review), we may publish your name, screen name and other information you have provided to us.

The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs or services.

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our publications and websites, and to enable us to customize your Internet experience. We also may use this information to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs or services.

We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request.

Agents and contractors of BizChickBlogs.com that have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for BizChickBlogs.com.

Please note that if BizChickBlogs.com is sold or otherwise disposed of, including through merger of, consolidation or sale of assets, the relevant customer database, including personally identifiable information we may possess about you, may, in whole or in part, be sold, disposed of, transferred or otherwise disclosed as part of that transaction.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice. Inadvertent disclosures may result, for example, when third parties misrepresent their identities in asking the site for access to personally identifiable information about themselves for purposes of correcting possible factual errors in the data.

**Privacy Options**

If you prefer not to receive e-mail marketing from this or any other BizChickBlogs.com property or any affiliated companies of BizChickBlogs.com, please email letters@bizchickblogs.com.

BizChickBlogs.com sites will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.

**Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors**

Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. You should consult the other sites’ privacy notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.  
BizChickBlogs.com sometimes may offer contests, sweepstakes, promotions, editorial features or other activities or offerings that are sponsored or co-sponsored by or presented with identified third parties. By virtue of your participation in such activities or offerings, your IP Address and the personally identifiable information that you voluntarily submit may be provided to both BizChickBlogs.com and the third parties. BizChickBlogs.com has no control over the third parties’ use of this information.

BizChickBlogs.com may use reputable third parties to present or serve advertisements, including online behavioral advertisements, that you may see on the web pages and to conduct research about the advertisements. This privacy notice does not cover any use of information that such third parties may have collected from you (e.g., type of browser, operating system, domain name, day and time of visit, page(s) visited) or the methods used by the third-parties to collect that information (e.g., cookies, web beacons and clear gifs).

**Cookies**

To enhance your online experience we use cookies. Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

We use cookies to understand Internet usage and to improve our content, offerings and advertisements. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs or services. Similarly, as part of an arrangement with our [business](http://www.bizchickblogs.com/yourbusiness) partners (including, those who present or serve the advertisements that you see on our web pages) we may also access cookies placed by others and allow others to access certain cookies placed by us.

We may also use small pieces of code such as “web beacons” or “clear gifs” to collect anonymous and aggregate advertising metrics, such as counting page views, promotion views or advertising responses. These “web beacons” may be used to deliver cookies that conform to our cookie policy.

**DoubleClick DART cookie**

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Our Commitment to Security**

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security and correctly use the information we collect.

**How You can Access or Correct Information**

To inquire about personally identifiable information that BizChickBlogs.com has collected about you, or how to correct factual errors in such information, please email info@bizchickblogs.com.

**Notice for Parents**

BizChickBlogs.com is not intended for use by children.

Changes to this notice may be changed by BizChickBlogs.com. The revised notice will be posted to this page so that you are aware of the information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about the BizChickBlogs.com privacy notice or its implementation please contact us via email by clicking here or at the following address:

BizChickBlogs.com  
2509 N Campbell PMB 73  
Tucson, AZ 85719

http://www.bizchickblogs.com/

This Privacy Notice was revised 12/23/2010.
